ZHIDANI RAMADHAN

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

085747108766 | zhidanir@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/zhidanir | zhidaniramadhan.vercel.app

Tangerang, Indonesia

Graduate from SMK Darussalam Balapulang, Tegal. Experienced as an Assistant Chief of Store and Drafter. Desire to switch career to web development field, because have a deep interest in technology development. Currently learning HTML, CSS/Tailwind, JavaScript, ReactJs, MySql and NodeJs at Harisenin.com Full-Stack Developer bootcamp to improve skills. A detail-oriented individual who is eager for a full-time opportunity in Full-Stack Web Development.

Work Experience

PT Xin Yi Industrial - Tangerang, Indonesia

Sep, 2022 - Present

DRAFTER

- Developing technical designs for shoe outsoles based on design specifications and functional requirements
- Including technical details such as tread pattern, outsole height and material specifications on technical drawings to facilitate production
- Knowing the characteristics of various types of materials and production techniques that can influence outsole design and performance

PT. Sumber Alfaria Trijaya Tbk - Tegal, Indonesia

Jul. 2020 - Jan. 2022

Assistant Chief Of Store

- Store operations were optimized and efficiency was increased
- Ensured administration ran well, such as: Monitored daily sales and compiled sales reports, Managed stock of goods and carried out inventory calculations, Managed financial administration, such as recording transactions and payments, Assisted in the process of receiving and releasing goods, Ensured compliance with company policies and procedures
- Created a pleasant shopping experience for customers and achieved sales targets

PT. Sumber Alfaria Trijaya Tbk - Tegal, Indonesia

Apr, 2019 - Jul, 2020

Crew Of Store

- Provided the best service to customers
- · Implemented work area cleanliness and safety standards
- · Contributed to achieving daily sales targets

Project Experiences

E-Commerce Web - Harisenin Project

Dec, 2023 - Present

FullStack Developer

- Developing a E-Commerce website using HTML, CSS, Javascript and NodeJs with the team
- Creating a CRUD app with ReactJs and NodeJs, self project
- Creating a E-Commerce website using ReactJs, self project

Education Level

SMK Darussalam Balapulang - Tegal, Indonesia

2015 - 2018

Courses, Training and Certifications

Harisenin.com - Tangerang, Indonesia

Dec, 2023 - Present

Full Stack Developer bootcamp

- Final Project: Designed and developed a website E-Commerce with a team
- Relevant Course works: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs and Node.js

Skills

Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, Tailwind, JavaScript, ReactJs

Soft Skills : Teamwork, Orientation to Detail, Problem Solving, Creativity, and Adaptability

Languages : Indonesian (Native), English (Intermediate)